Hello, I am Savita Maiti, an advisor [ __ ] product trainer at ICIC
Protens Live Insurance Company.
Today I will discuss with you
about ICICI Two Wishes. This wish plan is
specially designed for women which mainly
provides financial protection against certain important illnesses. This policy covers
all the diseases that I will discuss.
This wish plan can be made by a husband to his wife,
son to his mother, brother to his sister
or women
can also take the plan for themselves. That is, this plan is
not for men. It is only
for women. This plan has been brought because of some female diseases so
that women
are protected. Therefore,
all the diseases that I will discuss in this plan
are number one: breast cancer,
which is the most common cancer in women,
which can be cured if caught and treated at an early stage. Number
two: cervical
cancer. Number three: uterine
cancer.
This type of cancer occurs due to excessive cell growth in the uterus.
Number four: heart disease. The
risk of this heart disease is currently increasing day by day among women,
so coverage is available here due to heart disease.
This time, number five: number five:
Maternity complications, that is,
complications arising during this period of maternity, are
specifically covered for treatment.
Number six is ​​the newborn
birth defects, that is, the newborn birth defects.
This policy provides financial protection for other important illnesses relevant to women, such as
breast cancer,
skin
grafting, or
other things that are common in people who are burned,
when grafting is done in the entire area, when the
uterus is changed in such a place, the
money is available for this operation. That
is, 100% of the sum assured I have taken is
given as vital coverage and
50% of the sum assured is
given in the case of any surgical procedure and
25% of my maternity benefits, that is,
25% of the sum assured I have taken, I will be able to get for maternity benefits.
And it is also good to know
that to
take advantage of all these maternity benefits,
it is available after 365 days and
for other problems, 90 days i.e. 90
All these coverages are available after 90 days of the policy being launched. In
case of diagnosis of this disease, the
advantage of taking this policy by paying the lump sum is that
whenever my disease is diagnosed,
we will get the lump sum money
before the treatment. What is happening now, especially
for those who want to make financial preparations considering future health risks? This
policy is very important. It can be
taken as Limited Pay and Regular Pay.
Any one of the total
premiums is available free, that is, one
year of premium is free for women.
Thank you so much for today. Another day, we
can discuss another policy. But
yes, let me tell you what was not said. To
take this plan, women must be between the ages of
21 and 55, and to take the plan for maternity benefits,
women must be between the
ages of 21 and 37. Okay bye.